

CONTACT

- +389 78 854 466
- magdalenastefanovska@ gmail.com
- Skopje, North Macedonia
- in linkedin.com/in/magdalenajordanovska-1000/

SKILLS

- Game Design
- Game Level Design
- In-game Economy Design
- Game Mechanics Design
- Problem Solving
- Creativity
- Technical skills, drawing
- Communication skills
- Analytical skills

SOFTWARE

- Unity
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Unreal
- Photoshop

LANGUAGES

English (Advanced)

INTERESTS

- Drawing
- Photography

Magdalena Jordanovska

Game Designer

Creative and detail-oriented Game Designer with over 7 years of professional experience in designing hyper-casual, casual and puzzle games. Began career by crafting intircate levels and progressed to leading game design projects that achived top-chart success. Exellent communication, organicational and interpersonal skills. Highly motivated to contribute to the success of every project I join.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Game Designer – CrazyLabs Mar. 2019 – Mar. 2024

- Worked on the following games: Neon On, Bullet Man 3D, Fridge Organizing, Amaze, Dig Deep, Multi Maze 3D, Coin Rush, Light It Up and many others.
- Designing the in-game economy as well keeping the track of it according the data.
- Designing new levels in Unity maintaining and modifying them according to the data so the game gets to the top charts.
- Collaborating with the developers to do the proper changes in the games.
- Working with the artists for better visuality in some of the games.

Game Animator – Pickatale

Jan. 2018 – Mar. 2019

- Working with the artist on the artistic visual of the game.
- Designing the game environment with the artist.
- Animating the characters in the game

Sale Specialist – Anhoch

Jun. 2013 – Jul. 2017

- Sale specialist in high technology goods.
- Assist customers for purchases by identifying their needs in tech.
- Submitting orders and contributing to the sales team effort.
- Maintaining professional and technical knowledge.

Administrative Assistant – Termiko

Jan. 2012 – May 2013

• Preparation of the trade lists, business offers correspondence, monthly analysis and administrative documentation.

EDUCATION

Game Design Degree

Seavus Education & Development Center 2017 - 2018

Bachelor of Economics

University SS. Cyril and Methodius

2007 - 2012